Hey you're runnin' from what you can't escape
Come my way I'll put you under some kind of state
So watch me hypnotize you with my eyes
Make you fantasize about me tonight
I'm hypnotizing
Side to side got you hypnotized
Cause every time my clock tick-tock like this
Every little spell I cast don't miss
Always on top top top I'm hypnotizing
Got you doing what I want want want all night
Wake up to the click of sound
Follow with your eyes
Watch me watch me hypnotize
You'll be where I want you every night
You'll be back to feed your appetite
Swirling hypno disco illusion
My command becomes your reason
In your consciousness
Now your mind is of no consequence
I bet you never seen a girl so confident
Cut the compliments that's just common sense
I'm super shy, super shy
But wait a minute while I make you mine, make you mine
떨리는 지금도 You're on my mind all the time
I wanna tell you but I'm super shy, super shy
And I want to go out with you
Where you want to go (Huh?)
Find a lil spot, just sit and talk
Looking pretty, follow me
우리 둘이 나란히
보이지? 내 눈이
갑자기 빛나지
When you say I'm your dream
You don't even know my name, do ya?
누구보다도
나 원래 말도 잘하고 그러는데 왜 이런지
I don't like that
Something odd about you
Yeah, you're special and you know it
You're the top, babe
You're running from where you can't escape
I put you under some kind of state
I'm hypnotizing
Make you fantasize
Side to side, got you hypnotized